

Domagoj Lučić FRONTEND DEVELOPER

d.lucic14@gmail.com

Portfolio website

in @domagojlučić

ABOUT

I'm a frontend developer with more than 3 years of working experience in the field at Ericsson Nikola Tesla. I'm a coding enthusiast who is always eager to learn more and sharpen his coding skills. My biggest passion is ReactJS/Next.js.

SKILLS

Frontend Development

JavaScript - Advanced

ReactJS/Next.js - Advanced

HTML - Advanced

CSS - Advanced

TailwindCSS - Advanced

VBA - Advanced

Angular - Basic

Backend Development

Matlab - Basic

NodeJS - Basic

• UI/UX

Figma - Basic

Ant Design- Basic

LANGUAGES

• English - Expert

Work Experience

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Ericsson Nikola Tesla d.d.

Jan 2019 - Present

- VBA developer RNPT eMBB tool
- JavaScript/Angular/Matlab developer Gynt app
- Adding/removing features on the frontend/backend side of the applications
- Maintaining and improving existing code for frontend part of applications and storing data in the backend
- Assuring good UI/UX experience and working closely with sales representatives and research team
- Responsible for customer support via Helpdesk
- Testing

ASSISTANT CONSTRUCTION SITE SUPERVISOR

VMD Grupa d.o.o.

Jun 2016 - Oct 2018

- Worked as an assistant to one of the construction site supervisors on 3 different construction sites
- Supervised and assured quality and performance of other cooperator companies
- Administrative office work
- Managing clients (buyers)

STAFF

May 2013 - Dec 2017

Koncertna dvorana Vatroslav Lisinski

- Responsible for relations with people, controlling tickets, maintaining order and good behaviour during live events
- Physical work backstage in between different events

FREELANCE

No Stress Creative Studio

Jan 2018 - Present

- Event manager/Performer Theatre
- Dance instructor Plesni klub Atomic Dance Factory
- Dance instructor Plesni klub Point

Education

Mag.educ.phys.

Sep 2008 -Dec 2017

Prirodoslovno - Matematički fakultet, Zagreb

High school

Sep 2004 - Jun 2008

V. Gimnazija, Zagreb



Hard and Soft Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- ReactJS
- Next.js
- Typescript
- Angular
- Matlab
- TailwindCSS
- Bootstrap

- VBA
- Material UI
- Chakra UI
- Git
- NodeJS
- Sanity
- Jest
- Davinci Resolve
- Arduino UNO
- Microsoft Office

Personal Skills

- Good communication skills.
- Comfortable in working with people.
- Adaptive to new situations.
- Creative problem solving skills.
- Performance oriented.
- Hard working.
- Experience in working on large projects in a SCRUM-like environment with clients and colleagues from all over the world.

Other Skills

- Drivers licence category B
- Dance
- · Video recording and video editing

Certificates

JavaScript

- The Complete JavaScript Course 2022: From Zero to Expert (Udemy)
- instructor: Jonas Schmedtmann

ReactJS

- React The Complete Guide (Udemy)
- instructors: Maximillian Schwatrzmuller

HTML & CSS

- 50 Projects In 50 Days HTML, CSS & JavaScript (Udemy)
- instructors: Brad Traversy, Florin Pop



Portfolio website

@domagojlučić